OPEN_AI_ENDPOINT="your_openai_endpoint"
OPEN_AI_KEY="your_openai_api_key"
CHAT_MODEL="your_chat_model"
EMBEDDING_MODEL="your_embedding_model"
SEARCH_ENDPOINT="your_search_endpoint"
SEARCH_KEY="your_search_api_key"
INDEX_NAME="your_index"




In the code file, replace the following placeholders:
your_openai_endpoint: The Open AI endpoint from your project’s Overview page in the Azure AI Foundry portal (be sure to select the Azure OpenAI capability tab, not the Azure AI Inference or Azure AI Services capability).
your_openai_api_key The Open AI API key from your project’s Overview page in the Azure AI Foundry portal (be sure to select the Azure OpenAI capability tab, not the Azure AI Inference or Azure AI Services capability).
your_chat_model: The name you assigned to your gpt-4o model deployment, from the Models + endpoints page in the Azure AI Foundry portal (the default name is gpt-4o).
your_embedding_model: The name you assigned to your text-embedding-ada-002 model deployment, from the Models + endpoints page in the Azure AI Foundry portal (the default name is text-embedding-ada-002).
your_search_endpoint: The URL for your Azure AI Search resource. You’ll find this in the Management center in the Azure AI Foundry portal.
your_search_api_key: The API key for your Azure AI Search resource. You’ll find this in the Management center in the Azure AI Foundry portal.
your_index: Replace with your index name from the Data + indexes page for your project in the Azure AI Foundry portal